People who listened to our staff.
Today, we have Tsuchisaka Men.
Tsuchisaka Ger Oh, this is it! This is it!
Can I have tomorrow's gusas pulled out a little more?
Tomorrow is the day.
A little more than today.
A little.
Here we go.
One, two, one, two, three.
I'm having a hard time.
Yes, yes, a little
Yes, troubled
Troubled
Yes, hang in there
After this
Step in
One, two, one, two, three
Hold on to it
It's hard.
Right, so you practice right there.
You're going to get an A.
There was such a thing as being cramped and whatnot, but, yeah, you practice there. You know, you get the picture out.
Now please listen to this. Happy chocolate!
Cute!
Cute.
Hello.
I'm Carrie Tulle.
Thank you.
I'm not nervous, man.
But I'm certainly not talking.
Quiet.
She's nervous.
The doctor is watching over him.
We're both nervous.
I'm sure.
I'm nervous about everything.
He's looking at my cutest, best parts.
Oh! Annyongsuyu.
Wait a minute.
You're not wearing lipstick again.
You're not wearing lipstick.
Can I have the microphone, please?
Number two.
We've got a number. I'll take a look at it.
I can't wait to meet everybody.
I'm not as nervous as I used to be when I met everyone.
Okay.
Ah!
I'd feel less nervous if I met everyone who made a mistake.
Oh, I made a mistake.
Oh, no, I made a mistake.
I made a mistake.
I noticed that too.
Mystique?
We're at 5.5.
Yes, are you okay?
Yes, are you okay? Yes, okay.
Then let's move on.
So here we are, 19 members of our cute little lab.
Yay!
Should I say the announcement one more time?
Please do!
We will be going in chronological order, Fruit Zipper, Idolator Tutor Candy Tune.
And apart from the pre-registration for the four shows, the joint student evolvers of the three cute lab groups will be held today at 9:00 p.m. After this, there will be an announcement from the groups' official SNS and
QR code on the bulletin board on the front of the venue.
Please join us!
And Karen and Nachiko in the middle are in the back row.
Nachiko will be in the back row of the idols.
Shall we line up in the center?
Yes, ma'am.
And then, dedede dedede dedede dedede dedede dedede dedede dedede dedede dedede
Dedede, dedede, dedede, dedede, dedede, dedede, dedede, dedede, dedede, dedede, dedede, dedede, dedede, dedede, dedede, dedede, dedede... I'm going to go in front of you, so I'll start in the back and you'll see that I'm the prettiest girl you know.
I noticed that too.
I wonder if we could switch places and go to a "T" in the front.
Okay.
Are you okay? - Yeah.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
You think you can do it?
Okay, I'll try the swap.
Yeah, okay, quiet, swap.
Cute... don't tell me that's nice.
I don't want to be anyone but me.
No way.
I don't even know what that is.
I'm the type of person who likes to be told what to do.
It's easier for you to say.
I'll be waiting.
Please.
My cutest part.
Please, everyone, show me your cutest face.
Did you notice this? I was three years old when I was born... and I'm the prettiest thing you've ever seen... and you're crazy about me.
I'm done.
Okay, so, we'll see what happens next.
Ahh...
Um, here's the picture.Um, here is the picture.
And,
What kind of emotion do you want to enter?
The blackest one is...
This is the blackest one.
This is the one that I want to put in what kind of tone.
The darkest one.
I'm going to throw up.
I'm so nervous I'm going to throw up.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
Nasal and throat flu.
I caught it this morning.
What am I gonna do?
Doughnut doughnut doughnut
Donuts
Doughnuts
Ignored
Ignored lately
Pinching my nose
I've got it.
Five minutes and I'm in trouble.
It's gone.
Absolutely.
Please, please, please, please, please. Never! Never! If a guide is coming, it's me!
Please, please, please, please!
Oh no, some aspect of my nervousness is shaking.
I'll be counting on you.
Please take care of me.
Yes, I'm sure I'll be fine.
If you are quite nervous,
Sexy!
I'm Candy Tune.
Today is our debut live performance.
We may cause you a lot of trouble.
We hope that you will be with us for the whole day.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much.
Please take care of us.
Thank you very much. Performance in the middle of the show
If you have any orders in the middle, you can tell me in the middle.
Understood.
I'll take care of it.
People will laugh at me if I start pretending like this.
Me, too.
I'll be dropped into a grown-up's heart.
When you realize it...
I can't get out of it.
Just the two of us
Self-hidden taste
Balance Concept Most Glad Seino, Omochikon I Love the World One Gimbal to Kumanpon
ice cream rub
Dokaki kunpun
Even in space
My own
Shine my special dream
With you
I feel the future
That's why
I'll never change
♪ I'll never change ♪ ♪ The more I look at someone's words ♪
The more I think about all the things I can't say
♪ So, everybody, everybody, on our way ♪
I think about all the things I can't say I've been so swallowed up, it's all a big mess, all the details of the count...
Anyway, I'm feeling like today is just a little bit more...
I feel like we should just go through with the stage.
Please start saying cute warps to the audience.
Yes, sir.
Well, today is a full day.
Well, we'll try our best to condition ourselves a little more.
We look forward to working with you after this today.
Thank you very much.
Please take care of us.
When I was singing, I really thought I was in trouble,
I was relieved when I heard everyone's voice.
Please eat it instead of Rinomaru.
Hey, I brought my wallet that my mom gave me yesterday.
Yesterday, I was tiritanko'd at home.
I was so impressed with the skin on the chicken.
The skin is so delicious.
The skin is the best part.
Finally, on the day of my debut
I succeeded in eating fried chicken!
Oh! The rehearsal was warm and delicious!
I want my hair to be aced too... and everyone was taking pictures of me with my hair aced... and I want it...
I want it... maybe I was anxious in a place I didn't know... but I'm crying on my own.
I was so surprised. But I'm going to do my best and believe in you all.
Look at this.
It's cute.
The collaboration I just saw.
Really cute.
It's cute.
I'm looking forward to seeing it on stage.
I didn't see it earlier because I said that if I saw it now, everyone would get nervous, so I'm looking forward to seeing it in the show.
I'll do my best. I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.Thank you.
You look lovely.
Isn't that your 3rd night bath?
So what a cute lab!
We're finally at 19!
Nineteen!
I heard the sound of an idol letter being played live, and I popped!
Oh no, it's over!
I'm really getting into it. I think I'm getting nervous.
I'm really looking forward to it, but I might be getting really nervous.
Oh, my God!
He's so cute.
I just fell.
Hatsukarami
I'll do my best!
work hard together
Let's work hard together
I'm so nervous!
That makes me feel good!
I'm nervous!
You're so cute!
Nervous or sleepy?
Baby!
Either way!
I'll try my best!
I'm going to shoo your precious bangs!
Shush?
I'm going to shimmy! I don't really feel it... at all, but I'm nervous... because this monitor isn't right, Mr. Dreater... and I've been feeling sick inside since the moment we started.
I've been feeling sick inside since the moment the monitor started.
It's not good, is it?
We've been walking all over the place.
Right now...
It's like an abusive relationship.
We were exchanging Instagrams.
Karen... Nachi...
Nachi?
Nachire.
We were exchanging Instagrams.
About a week later.
I saw you here.
Karen?
I saw her here about a week after we exchanged instagrams and asked her to hang out with me. I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get the most out of your time here.
If you don't get the rhythm right on your face, you'll just keep doing the same thing even if you put your foot in the wrong place.
If the girl in front makes a mistake, the girl in the back can make a little adjustment.
Check the width.
Let's go for it.
It's okay.
You don't have to work so hard.
Just have fun.
Let's have fun! Just have fun.
Have fun! Have fun!
Have fun, just like yesterday.
That's right.
Gerard, you're going to have so much fun.
Let's see your face. Let's see your face.
We can have fun.
I can't enjoy it.
I'm not having fun. You're crying. Let's see your face. Don't say that. Don't say it.
Don't say it.
Why, what, did you cry?
Yay.
I was crying just now.
You were crying earlier?
Yeah, I was crying earlier.
I'm not worried about you singing well, but rather enjoying yourself and doing it in a way that your voice is still in tune, so I'm not worried at all.
I'm sure you'll be fine if you're all cheerful.
I'm so scared that I'm going to cry so hard because I feel like I've already cried a lot during the rehearsal.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all!
I'll do my best!
Catch you all!
I'm so nervous.
I've never smelled anything like this before, but then again, love lives on, love lives on.
Love live. Love live.
Love Lives! Love Lives!
You're a genius idol.
You do everything right.
At last.
Thank you very much. I'm so nervous. I'll do my best!
I'll do my best!
I'm sorry.
Candidating is about to begin.
CANDLING begins!
CANDING begins!
Here comes the caning!
CANDLING CANDLING CANDLING CANDLING CANDLING CANDLING CANDLING CANDLING CANDLING
I'm sorry.
Here comes the candy!
Tune it up, tune it up, tune it up, tune it up
Chew.
After everything we've done today, nothing can go wrong.
We've practiced so much.
I'll be fine.
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best. Skyning!
How do you do? We're Skyning! Nice to meet you! 🎵Debut 7
Yes, we've finished our debut 7!
Yay!
Woo!
Did everyone have a good time?Did everyone have a good time?
It was fun!
I'm glad, first of all, I have a great sense of accomplishment. We all had a lot of lessons until today,
I'm really happy that we made it here today, and that we were able to finish without any problems.
I hope you will all continue to support us.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
Thank you.